

LEARNING AND DEVELOPMENT
EXECUTIVE

### **Details**

Ahmedabad

India

7600965134

khushigehlot48@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Indian

DATE OF BIRTH

02/08/1996

### **Skills**

Tally

Microsoft Office

### **Hobbies**

Listening Music Travelling

### Languages

English

Gujarati

Hindi

### **Profile**

Enthusiastic & Dedicated Learning & Development professional, with over 2 year experience in a fast paced Human Resource department. Motivated Professional with a drive for serving as a dedicated support specialist and energetic team member. Experienced in managing Induction & Orientation of newly joined employees and dedicated towards the mission of a company.

# **Employment History**

### Trainee, Adani Realty, Ahmedabad

MARCH 2022 - MARCH 2023

- Assisted Learning & Development Head in day to day activities.
- Independently handled the Induction & Orientation program for new joiners.
- To coordinate complete process of Induction and ensure each employee's under goes the complete module of Induction and issuance of certificates to all Inductees is done
- Collaborated with external resources such as training agencies/external trainers, community colleges and Universities for various training.
- To keep the L & D document deck well maintained with all the documents related to training like Training SOP, Employee Training files & records, Training Manuals.
- Designing and implementing the Training Calendar for the year based on training needs identification.
- Budgeting, organizing, and coordinating training workshops on technical skills,
   Behavioral skills, soft skills, culture training, etc.
- Monitoring the quality of training, assessing training effectiveness and suggest modifications based on the feedback received.
- Coordinated for the New Joiner "Buddy" Orientation program.

#### Human Resource Executive. Handee Man. Ahmedabad

FEBRUARY 2019 - JUNE 2021

- Organized new employee orientation schedule for New Hires.
- Maintaining Employee Records.
- Supported daily operations of Human Resource Department.

## Education

B.Com, H.L College of Commerce, Ahmedabad

JUNE 2014 - MAY 2016

M.Com, Neel Deep College of Commerce, Ahmedabad

MAY 2016 - JULY 2018

### References

Anshul Agnihotri from Adani Realty

aanshul2020@gmail.com | 7574802989

Vaibhavi Gajjar from Enbee Education Centre

vaibhavigajjar11@gmail.com | 8866539526